ほらみんな夢中だ
リクが…
ゴングを…！
“Now you see her Now you don’t”
死ぬかもしれねぇな…
“See her？” “No I don’t”
輸血はここまでだ… 血がたりねぇ…
十分です 体が軽くていい
ほら もっと欲張って
うっ… 普通なら気絶してるぜ…
ほら もっとよく見て
二人の力は風神雷神のごとく拮抗…
艦隊率いるあいつはまさしく
生まれる前からエイリアン
アダムとイブの再来ならば
宇宙規模での勘違いだけどね
ミクロとマクロの距離感大事
COSMOS vs ALIENの戦い
いつでもマーベラス
勝負の行方は霧の中…
と思われていたが
命を賭した戦いが
今始まろうとしていた…！
荒川王様ゲーム 決勝戦は
シスターVSマリア！
猫もしゃくしもいっそこのままで
いんじゃない？
シスターはマリアの先制毒舌攻撃により
大出血 すでに瀕死の状態であった！
Chapter 190: "Arakawa King Game Finals"
ほら そっと手を取って
The final match in this Arakawa King
Game is Sister versus Maria!
ほら とっとと笑って
They're evenly matched, making the outcome
completely unpredictable. However!
トークトークのBPMは
とうにジョークの域を超えて
Sister has almost bled out from Maria's
preemptive mental assault.
山超えて 谷超えて
あいつのいる星に届く
ほらきっと霧中だ
キャプテン・クィーンにSOS
ミサイル迎撃準備よし
That's all the blood we have. We need more.
弾道操るあいつはいかにも
生まれる前からエイリアン
いままさに宇宙は SPACE
It's more than enough. Less blood makes
me light on my feet, anyway.
いわゆるひとつのSWEET
Ring the bell.
甘い甘い宇宙のTASTE
A normal man would be unconscious.
いわゆるひとつのSWEET
He might just die...
魔法をひとふり あの子と二人きり
Rec, I mean.
砂糖をひとふり あの子はいただき
A fierce battle with lives on
the line is about to begin!
Chapter 191: "Duel of the Fates"
はむっ！ チュ～～ッ！
はっ！ チュ～～ッ！ んっ
It begins now!
それでは今からーっ！
Unlimited weapons, no rules, no referee!
The King Game finals begin now!
武器の制限解除 ルール無用
レフェリー不要の王様ゲーム決勝戦を行う！
Fight!
ファイッ！
ップハー！ ハァ…
I didn't expect you to volunteer
to give blood like that.
まさかテメーが自ら
血液提供者に名乗り出るとはな…
ハァ… でっ 当ったり前だろ！
何が何でもシスターに勝ってもらわないと
Of course I volunteered! I need Sister to win!
マリアさんが王様になったら 俺とお前なんて
絶対カースト制度の一番下行きだぞ！
What do you think will happen if Maria wins?!
She'll create a caste system and
put us on the bottom rung!
Well, I don't want that either.
あぁ… 俺だって
そんな事態はごめんだ…
But Sister is in love with Maria!
けどよ… シスターはマリアに
惚れてんじゃねーか！
How could he point a gun
at the woman he loves?!
好きな女に銃向けられるもんか！？
何を言う 星… 以前お前も
言っていたではないか
What are you saying, Hoshi?
Didn't you tell me before?
You have to just attack the woman you love!
惚れた女には アタックあるのみとな！
ミサイルアタックでとは
思いもよらねェーー！
We had no idea it would be a missile attack!
He totally misunderstood what I meant,
but I'm glad he's going all-out.
完全に色々はき違えてるけど
やる気になってくれてるならそれで…
いや 殺る気すぎじゃねーか！？
No, this is way too far!
Even Maria couldn't—
あれじゃ いくらマリアさんでも
本当に死…
Too slow.
のろいわね… 生まれたての
子羊の方が まだ速いわよ！
A newborn lamb is faster than that!
Well done. It seems you haven't lost your edge.
さすがだ… 衰えていないようだな
You're still worthy of your alias-
Beautiful Missile Interceptor.
“美しきミサイル迎撃装置”と
呼ばれていた頃のウデは
ウフフ… あなたも昔のまま…
You haven't changed, either.
You still rely too much on firepower.
まだ銃に頼りきりなのね…
うっ！？ それは！
That's—
Battle Shears Final Attack! Sazae's Father!
戦場鋏術（きょうじゅつ）奥義
“サザエズファザー”！
What's this feeling?
何だ！？ この感じ…
Just seeing her stance gives me a
chill right on the top of my head!
あの構えを見ただけで…
頭部を中心とした寒気が…！
At that moment, all the men watching
imagined the exact same hair style.
その時全員の脳内に 同じ男の
ヘアースタイルが浮かんでいたと言う…
Chapter 192: "Glass Heart"
I heard about this before.
わし… 昔 聞いた事があるんじゃ…
The reason why Sister has such a poker face...
シスターのポーカーフェイスの理由…
“サザエズファザー”を受け
After being hit with Sazae's Father, the rest of
his platoon wouldn't stop laughing at him.
部隊に帰った時の
隊員達の止まらない嘲笑…
It was enough to drive all emotional
expression from Sister's mind!
それは シスターから表情を
奪うのに十分じゃったと…
うえええ～ん
If I knew his heart was made of glass,
そんなガラスハートなら 出会い頭に服装を
思いっきり笑ってやればよかったですよ
I would have laughed right in his face
when I first saw him in drag.
Chapter 193: "The Voice of God"
I hope Sister will be okay...
大丈夫かなぁ シスター君…
If he's seen the attack before,
he should be able to avoid it now.
けど 一度くらっているなら二度は…
違うな… 力のぶつかり合いなら
シスターの勝ちだろう…
No.
If it were a matter of raw strength,
Sister would win.
But Maria insulted him right away
to take that strength away.
だが マリアの狙いは まず
毒舌で体力を奪い
Then she dug up a traumatic memory,
continuing to chip away at his will to fight.
そして 凶悪な必殺技の存在により
トラウマを植え付け
戦意を削ぐ事にある
Sister is shaking!
シスターが震えてる！？
He won't be able to hit a thing like that!
あれじゃ 弾は当たらないぞ
くっ それでなくても
はじかれてるっていうのに！
Even if he weren't shaking,
she can deflect all his shots!
He'll never win the fight like this!
このままじゃシスターが負けちゃうよ！
むっ！？ はっ 聞こえる…！
神の声が聞こえるぞ！
I can hear it! I can hear the voice of God!
Where'd that come from?
な 何言ってんだ？ 急に…
Is his fear making him hallucinate?
恐怖のあまりの幻聴だろ…
Is he okay?
だ 大丈夫でござるか！？
My Lord...
神よ…！ “目を覚ませ”
“銃を捨てよ”とは一体…！？
"Open your eyes"? " Throw down
your gun"? What do you mean?
It might be the real thing!
やばい！ アレ本物かも！
What? "You were wrong about so much"?
何…？ “色々間違えている”と…？
ああーっ！ ものすごく言って欲しかった
言葉だけど 今はやめて欲しい！
That's what I've always wanted someone
to say to him, but now's not the time!
Sister! Don't listen!
シスター！ 耳を貸しちゃダメです！
I thought you only believed
in what your bullets can hit!
自分の弾の当たるもの以外
信じないんじゃなかったんですか！？
I am a servant of God. His voice is absolute.
私は神のしもべ… 神の声は絶対だ
At every moment in my life, it is
the voice of God that saved me.
どんな時も 私を助けてくれたのは
この神の声…
I will adhere to your command.
あなたの声に従います
Sister...
シスター…
"Throw down your gun."
“銃を捨てよ” “ナイフを持て”
"Take up your knife."
“接近戦はＣＱＣ”！
"Get in close and use CQC!"
"Semper Fi!" Right, my Lord?!
“センパーファイ”ですね 神よ！
God never gives such specific advice!
神様はそんな的確な
アドバイスはしねーよ！
His silhouette suggests another legendary figure.
シルエットからして 違う伝説の人です
Chapter 194: "Lethal Weapon"
とにかくお願いします シスター！
マリアさんにだけは絶対勝って下さい！
We're counting on you, Sister!
You have to beat Maria, no matter what!
He dodged her point-blank attack!
あの至近距離からの攻撃を避けた！？
No! Maria was just trying to pin him to the pillar!
いや違う！ マリアが狙ったのは
柱にシスターをぬいつける事だ！
なっ！？ シスターの服が
床にめり込んだぞ！
Sister's clothes put a hole in the ring!
Wearing weights during a fight?
What are you thinking?
重しなんて着込んで戦って…
一体何のつもり？
It's a handicap.
ハンデだ
What's going on? They just stopped moving.
ど どうしたんだ？ 急に
動かなくなっちまったぞ
あ…っ 見ろ！ リングの上が
いつの間にか血の海になっているぞ！
Look! There's blood everywhere!
Where'd that come from?
How? Why? They're not moving at all!
一体どうして… 全然動いてないのに！
No, they're fighting.
違う…！ 二人は戦っている…！
You just can't see them fighting at light-speed,
so they seem frozen to you.
超高速での戦いに目がついていかず
止まって見えるだけ…
Is that even possible?
そんな事が！？
I guess I'm the only one here who
can follow their movements.
どうやらこの会場で二人の動きが
見えているのは 俺だけのようだな
Nay, I can see it, too.
いいや 拙者にも見えているでござる！
R-Really?!
え？ え？ そうなの！？
俺には全く見えねェ…
I can't see a thing.
だ だよなぁ！？ 俺にも
ただ止まってるようにしか…
Yeah! They look totally motionless to me, too!
But!
だが！ 魂で感じるぜ…
炎と炎のぶつかり合いを…！
I can feel it in my heart! The burning
flames of their souls are clashing!
You can do it!
が… がんばれ…
-あ…！ がんばれ！ 二人共がんばれ！
-二人共がんばれ！
Yeah, you can do it!
Both of you!
うう… そうだ！ どっちも真の漢だ！
Yeah! You're both awesome!
You two are the greatest! Maria! Sister!
カッコイイわよ マリア！ シスター！
もう 勝ち負けなんてどうでもいいぜ！
I don't care who wins anymore!
This competition of pure strength is too beautiful!
素敵だぞ！ 純粋に
強さを求める者達よ！
お… はっ！ 純粋に強さを…
Pure strength...
Right. Those two probably don't care
about the throne or giving orders.
そうか… あの二人には もう王座だとか
特権だとか どうでもいいのか…
They're using this battle as a chance
to test their own personal limits!
今 この時が自らの証明…
これが… 戦い…
ああっ シスター！
Sister!
Maria!
マリアー！ あ～～ぁ
お前ら二人ともっ 本当の漢…
You guys truly chiv—
You have B.O.
汗臭い カブト虫の臭いがする
人間と同じ格好してるんじゃないわよ
You smell like a dung beetle. How dare
you dress like a human being?
Huh? Maria? What happened
to the light-speed battle?
あれ…？ マリアさん…
高速移動は…？
Where's the burning flames?
魂のぶつかり合いは…？
あら 何の事？
What do you mean?
I was just kindly putting Sister in his place.
私はいつも通り 口で優しくシスターに
自分の身の程を教えていただけよ？
Also...
それと… マリアさんじゃなくて
女王様と呼びなさい
Don't call me Maria. Call me Queen.
ひゃああっ！
Witness the birth of a new empress.
ここに 女帝誕生です
Chapter 195: "Maria's Decree"
The final round of the Arakawa King Game ended
with everyone's greatest fear victorious-
荒川王様ゲームが決勝戦を終え
王座についたのは 何と
一番恐れられていたマリアだった！
Maria!
ホラどうしたのリク君
私の命令を発表してちょうだい
What are you doing, Rec?
Hurry up and announce my decree.
おい どうしたんだよ リク
何て書いてあんだよ それ…
Hey, what's wrong, Rec? What's it say?
こ… こんな… こんな命令が
許されると思っているのか…！
C-Can...
Can we really allow this order?!
That order is absolute.
これは… 絶対命令よ
う… ぜ… 全荒川住人に告ぐ！
To...
To all residents of Arakawa!
M
a
Make clothes for the sheep, which have
all been feeling cold recently.
k
e
寒がりの羊さん達のために
お洋服を作ってあげなさい
c
l
o
c
l
o
t
h
e
s
f
o
r
f
o
r
t
h
e
t
h
e
s
h
e
p
w
h
i
c
h
i
c
h
a
v
e
h
a
v
e
a
l
b
e
n
f
e
l
i
n
g
c
o
l
d
r
e
c
n
t
c
e
n
t
l
y
何それ！？ どういう暗号！？
Chapter 196: "Man's Work"
When she says "sheep," does she mean us?
羊って言うのは
俺達を指しているとか…？
Do the "clothes" refer to some
kind of torture device?
お洋服と言うのは 何かの拷問器具の事を
指しているとかでござるか…？
Oh, well I don't mind going along
with your interpretation.
あらあら あなた達が解釈した通りに
実行してもいいのよ？
ひいっ！ あ… う…
ふぅ… ちょっと前の暑い日に
羊達の毛を刈っちゃったんだけど
I sheared my sheep's wool on an
especially hot day a while ago.
But remember how that cold snap came through?
何だか また寒さが
戻っちゃったでしょ？
That's why I wanted to make them some
clothes using the wool I collected.
だから刈った毛でお洋服を
作ってあげたかったのよ うふっ
Wow, Maria! You really take care
of everyone in your territory!
さすがマリアじゃ！ シマのもんの世話を
しっかり見とるんじゃのう！
Making clothes sounds like fun!
You'll really let us help?
お洋服作りなんて楽しそ～！
それ 手伝わせてもらえるの？
Of course. That's my order to you.
もちろん 命令だもの
おお～ 洋服というのは
毛から出来ていたのだな
I didn't know clothes were made from hair.
うふふ そうよ
That's right.
Then Maria...
ならば マリア！
Can you shave my head and make
a tummy warmer out of it?!
私の毛も まるごとガツンと
腹巻きにして欲しいんだが！
It'll make my head lighter and
keep my stomach warm!
頭は軽いし お腹も冷えない！
A golden tummy warmer!
まあ 金色の腹巻き！
Please reconsider, Nino!
ニノさん！ 考え直して！
でもニノちゃん それじゃ
頭が冷えちゃうわよ？
But then, don't you think your head will get cold?
Oh, true.
おお そうか
腹巻きなら 別に作ってあげる
I'll make one for you special later.
またあんな良心的な事を
言ってるでござるよ
Did you hear that? She's being really nice...
This can't be. I thought when Maria took
the throne, she'd say something like...
ありえない… マリアさんが
女王の座についたら
“荒川の水を全て血に変えよ”
くらい言うはずなのに！
"Turn the water of the Arakawa River to blood!"
You think I'm some kind of monster?
私を どこの魔族だと
思ってるのかしらね
I only joined in because it looked like fun.
I didn't have any particular wish or anything.
ただ楽しそうだったから出ただけで
特に願いはなかったのよ
That's terrible in itself!
それはそれで酷いでござる！
Well...
だって… 今までの人生からじゃ
考えられないくらい 今がとても幸せだもの
I'm happy with what I have now. I'm grateful,
considering the other things I've experienced.
Now, everyone! I need you to put the
wool in hot water to soften it up!
さぁみんな！ まずは羊毛を
お湯でほぐしてちょうだい
Okay!
はーい！
あの人の過去は私もよくは知らんが
確かに善人ではない
I don't know too much about her past,
but I know she's not a virtuous person.
But if she were truly evil, the animals
wouldn't like her the way they do.
だが悪人であれば あんな風に
動物達がなつきもせん
That's how I see it, anyway.
と 私は思うぞ
まぁ… そりゃ…
I guess...
We never thought of her as
some evil mastermind.
俺達も極悪人とまでは
思ってねェけどさ…
うむ…
んっ… あー！ じゃあ
俺達も手伝うかなー！
Jeez! Fine, let's go help.
It's an order!
命令だしなー！
Verily!
ござるなー！
Why, thank you.
まあ！ 三人ともありがとう！
But I have another job for the men.
でも男の子には
他の仕事を頼みたいのよ
I need you to go over there...
あなた達は向こうで…
犬になりなさい
and be my dogs.
Dogs
Dogs?
Your job is to chase the sheep. I even
made you something special for it.
羊を追うお仕事よ
頑張ってもらおうと思って 私
みんなにプレゼントを用意したの
Now pick the collar you like,
and get down on your knees.
さっ 好きな首輪をして
地面に這いつくばりなさい
Maria looked very happy at that moment.
マリアは本当に幸せそうでした
Chapter 197: "A Dog's Life"
Don't worry. It's an easy job.
大丈夫 簡単な仕事よ
I just need you to get the sheep I put
out to pasture back into the pen.
河川敷で放牧されている羊達を
柵の中に戻して欲しいの
Take a look at your betters over
there and learn from them.
やり方は 先輩方の動きを見て
技を盗んでね
They're moving around really strangely!
むちゃくちゃな動きしてますよ！
大丈夫 誰にでも初めてはあるわ
Don't worry. There's a first time for everything.
無理せず 真似できるところから
真似していけばいいの
Just try to mimic whatever parts of it you can.
あ… マリアさん…
Maria...
Now hurry up and get on all fours.
だから さっさと這いつくばれって
言ってるのよ
ひっ え… いや… そんな事したら
速く動けないし…
B-But if I do that, I won't be able
to move very fast, and...
What are you talking about? Just look at Sister.
何言ってんの ホラ
シスターを見てみなさい
は 速ぇーーっ！ つかそれ
もうホフク前進じゃないですかー！
He's super fast! And he's doing a military crawl!
Don't just stand there!
貴様らァ！ 何つっ立ってる！
そっちに向かったぞ！
They're inbound! Unleash cover
fire and intercept them!
威嚇して迎撃せんかァ！
Cover fire?! What does that mean?!
ちょっ… 威嚇って どうすれば…
Use your glare! Make it look like
you want to eat them alive!
目で殺せ！ 食い殺す程の
表情を作るのだ！
んな無茶な！ しかも
超突っ込んでくるよ！ うわっ
You're talking crazy!
They're coming right at me!
わうっ！ わうっ！ わうっ！ わうっ！
おお…っ！？ お～ 助かった…！
Whew!
He's like a real pro.
さすがプロでござるな！
Good dog...
お～し よしよし 良くやった…
わうっ
はうっ！
おっ その表情はいいんじゃないか？
You have the right idea with that expression.
あ… ホントだ 羊が逃げてく
You're right. The sheep are backing down.
It's kind of funny seeing them run away.
ちゃんと逃げてくと 面白いな
Sir Hoshi! Your face returned to normal...
星殿！ 顔が戻っているでござるよ
Stay alert! Think about the worst parts of
humanity and society, and maintain that face!
気を抜くんじゃない！ 人生や社会の
暗い部分だけを見つめて その顔を維持するんだ
W-We'll try.
や やってみます！
A biased judicial system... the catch-22
of trying to find a wife...
見直されない裁判制度…
本末転倒の婚活…
Urban decay... the doughnut effect...
Failed community development...
社会の闇… ドーナツ化現象…
空回りする村おこし…
明治維新… 近江屋事件… 刀傷…
The Meiji Restoration... the Omiya
Incident... katana scars...
Good! Keep it up! Move toward
the fence from 2 o'clock!
いいぞ！ その調子だ！
そのまま２時の方向の柵へ向かえ！
Starboard! I'm not sensing enough despair!
右舷 絶望感薄いぞ！
よしっ！ 今だ！
全軍前方の羊に突撃ー！
Now! All hands, charge the sheep!
ぬああーーっ！
Chapter 198: "Counting Sheep"
Did you guys round up the sheep?
あら～！ この羊集めたの
リク達なの？
Good job!
お疲れさま！
We're done making the clothes, too.
わしらの方も服作り終了じゃ！
ん？ 何故そんなに沈んでいるんだ？
Why do they look so depressed?
Sister.
-シスター
-は？
最後にこの名簿とタグを照らし合わせながら
羊を数えてもらえる？
For your final task, I need you to match their tags
to this name list while you count the sheep.
All right.
了解した
まぁ シスター 羊を数えるなんて
Sister's going to count the sheep?
寝ちゃいけんかんなー！
You better not fall asleep!
あー… デヴィッド…
サイード… トム…
David, Zaeed, Tom...
んあ？ 何かずいぶんカッコイイ名前が
多いですね まるで人名…
Those are interesting names for sheep.
They sound like human names...
Huh? Of course they do. Because they're all...
え？ まぁ それはそうよ…
だって全部… 私が今までに
愛した男の名前だもの
the names of men I've loved.
カール… シロウ… ヒュー…
Carl, Shiro, Hugh...
Dusty, Raleigh...
ダスティ… ローリー…
Sister! If you keep counting those sheep,
you'll fall asleep and never wake up again!
シスター！ それ以上その羊を数えたら
目覚める事のない眠りに落ちてしまいますよ！
Chapter 199: "Clean White Lines"
Ah, I'm glad they fit so well.
おお 良かった！ みんなぴったりだ
Now the crazy sheep won't catch cold!
これで風邪をひかんで済むのう！
きさんら！
マリアの命令 無事遂行だわ～！
We officially carried out Maria's decree!
I get the feeling us guys were
given the real decree...
明らかにメインの命令は
俺達に下されてた気がする！
お～い みんな～！
川岸に集まってくれないかー
Hey, everyone!
Can you gather by the riverbank?
It's time for the closing ceremony!
最後のシメだよ～！
We're going to release everyone's
decrees out into the river.
みんなが書いた命令書を
川に流すぞー！
ぬあっ！
You kept them?!
それ まだ持ってたのかよ！
Nooo!
いや～！
見ちゃダメー！
Don't look!
わ～ん！
ハハハハ… 早くおいで！
Hurry up!
All right!
おーし！ みんな 川に向かって敬礼！
Everyone! Face the river, and salute!
いやぁ でもアレですよね…
But you know, when you think about it...
やっぱりこういう事は自力で
叶えるもんですよね…
These wishes only really have meaning
when you achieve them on your own.
おっ リク 言うじゃねーか
That's a nice quote.
Well, I'm a mature adult who knows
what's proper and what's not...
まぁ… 俺もその辺ふまえた
大人の男ですから… ハハハハ…
ん？ ここに引っ掛かってるやつ
リクの字じゃねーの？
Something's caught over here.
Isn't this Rec's handwriting?
Everyone
except Nino
has to
speak
to me with
utmost
respect!
Everyone
except Nino
has to
speak
to me with
utmost
respect!
うわァ…
ひくわー…
This is too...
どーにも…
Don't take it out of the water!
水あげすんじゃねーよ！ だったら…
Fine, then this one must be yours!
これとか ぜってーオメェじゃねーの？
ちっさ ぷっ
What a tiny little dream!
ニノさん？
ナハハハ… みんなここに引っ掛かって
わやくちゃになってるよ
Everyone's papers got caught over here.
They'll dissolve sooner or later.
まーまー そのうち溶ける紙だからよ
I feel like a fool!
生き恥じゃねーか！
What's embarrassing about your own wish?
自分の願いを恥とか言っちゃいけねーよ
That's not even it!
いや だからそういう事以前に…
Nino? What are you doing?
ニノさん！ 何をしてるんですか？
あ！ そんなとこにも引っ掛かってる
Oh, something's caught over there.
It's all right, Nino!
大丈夫です ニノさん！
リク…？
Rec?
Do you remember when I went out
like this to unsnag that grass boat?
前もこんな風に草舟を取りに
行った事がありましたよね
But this time I'm not gonna fall in.
俺 もう転びませんよ
I know how fast the current is over here.
ここの流れが速い事も知ってますし
底の石が滑りやすいのも分かってます
I know how slippery the rock is over there.
I even learned how to swim
in the river quite well. And...
川での泳ぎ方も結構覚えました
あと… ニノさんが寂しいと思ってる時の顔も
なんとなく分かるようになりました
Whenever you're feeling sad... now I can tell.
Rec...
リク…
I want
to be
with
everyone.
だから大丈夫です！
It'll be all right!
Let's always be together.
Right now, and forever after!
ずっと 一緒にいましょう！
今も昔も これからもずっと…！
地球人の俺と… みんなと！
With me, the Earthling, and everyone else!
ずっと一緒にいましょう！
Let's always be together!
Okay!
Whenever I search for a taste of love
Ai no kakera sagasutabi ni
愛のカケラ 探すたびに
I get sad, and I just wish I could tell you why
itsumo nazeka sabishikunaru
いつも何故か 寂しくなる
I should get going now
mou ikanakucha
もう行かなくちゃ
Before the sky opens up and weeps for me
kono sora nakidasumae ni
この空泣き出す前に
Everything tossed everywhere
barabara ni natte
バラバラになって
Searching for your laughing voice
sono koe wo sagashite
その声を探して
And before we knew what had hit us
itsunohi ka bokura wa
いつの日か僕らは
We found we were seeking each other
otagai wo motometeku
お互いを求めてく
Every single passing day
sarasara ni natte
さらさらになって
Seemed to trickle through my hands
nagareteku mainichi
流れてく毎日に
And before we knew what had hit us
itsunohi ka bokura wa
いつの日か僕らが
We had found ourselves within this place
tadoritadoritsuku basho
たどりたどり着く場所
It's always passing by, this thing I never reach
tayorinakunatte tsukamenakute
頼りなくって 掴めなくて
I get so afraid, I just can't sleep at night
fuan ni natte nemurenakute
不安になって 眠れなくて
Then I screamed out loud so you would never leave
ohgoe wo dashita hanarenaide
大声を出した 離れないで
Always stay by my side, please don't ever go away
hanarenaitte zutto soba ni itene
離れないって ずっと側にいてね
Please don't leave me now
hanarenaide
離れないで
Chapter 200: "Applaud You"
I know it's just a magic trick.
タネも仕掛けもあるんだろう
Even so, I can't take my eyes off the stage.
それでも… 僕は
舞台から 目が離せない
I already threw out the binoculars I use
to figure out how the tricks work.
マジックの秘密を暴くための
双眼鏡は もう捨てた
No matter how long I stared,
it was too bright for me to see.
目を凝らしても 眩しくて
何も見えなかったから
The trick that shed those tears.
涙を流すからくりも
The secrets hidden in the lion's cage.
全ての秘密は ライオンの檻の中
Even after you showed me everything,
君の見せてくれる全てに
今はただ われるような拍手を
all I could do was give you
my deafening applause.
I didn't want you to go back behind the curtain.
幕の向こうに君を帰さぬよう
I didn't want the circus to leave.
サーカスを帰さぬよう
All I can do now is applaud
you, as if it were a prayer.
今はただ 祈りのような拍手を
Illustration: Hikaru Nakamura
ENDCARD GALLERY
Hekiru Hikawa
Hiroyuki
Yuto
Ken Yagami
Jiro Suzuki
Takahiro Seguchi
Renjuro Kindaichi
Yukiko Sumiyoshi
Kaworu Watashiya
Ahn Dongshik
Masked Brothers
We'll protect the riverbank's peace!
Yana Toboso
Hikaru Nakamura
Jin Kobayashi
Taro★Mino
Oh!Great
Nasou Shoha
Lily Hoshino
Makoto Tsuchibayashi
Shigeto Koyama
Kinu Nishimura
Go Nagai
Hiromu Arakawa
Yusuke Kozaki
Arina Tanemura
Hikaru Nakamura